It's the Great era of piracy.
Ambitious people were unleashed on the sea in search of wealth,fame, and power.
For the pirates, this is an age of dreams.
But among them, some only enjoyed plunder.
For the powerless, this meant endless days of oppression.
The marines, under the jurisdiction of the world government,couldn't save all the powerless ones.
Then, who could they depend on? What could they do to be saved?
We are really in a fix Nobody cares about people like us.
All I do is cry.
Everyone says so. Pirates are bad, but what's worse is...
I'm so hungry
Of course. Because the pirates took it all away.
Yes, the pirates,
Because of those selfish brutes,nobody can have any fun.
Do you understand now?
I'm begging you, do something to ease our suffering.
You're the only one! The only one!
Please
You're the only one
I'm begging
Only you can do it.
Please
I know. I know it.
I'll make a new era for you where everyone is happy.
Where are our seats?
I have to buy some merch!
What a long queue!
I'm going to need the toilet soon. Wow, your seats included a meal?
Yeah, platinum tickets!
Wow, aren't there a lot of people here?
It's because this is the first time Uta will sing live in front of her fans.
Until now, we've only ever seen her on video transponder snail!
Seeing Uta live, and in a beautiful place like this! I just...!
There are even merfolk here! This seems really fun, but why do we have to dress like this?
To make her first concert more exciting, you can get one of these if you wear a costume!
Oh, is that why?
I can't wait!
She's the most loved person in the world right now, after all.
Is she really that amazing?
i know it's odd coming from the Soul King himself,
but her singing is from another dimension.
U! T! A! Uta
Ridiculous- Uh?
Damn swordsman! Come back here and say that again! I'll grill you up good and juicy
I'd like to see you try curly
Heeeey! It's starting!
The concert is starting! Luffy!
♫ We can choose the way of our future ♫
♫ Try a brand new path ♫
♫ If I change the world... ♫
♫ Say goodbye to everyone who stands against us ♫
♫ No one has the power to stop a change that comes through music ♫
♫ No, you can't stop magic ♫
♫ Close your eyes and you can see the future before you ♫
♫ Every note I sing is bringin' you closer to your purposes ♫
♫ Once you're there don't let go ♫
♫ You wanna play a real game, unfurl the chain ♫
♫ Melody strung out like we're walkin' on a tight rope ♫
♫ Don't wanna cry, don't wanna try, wanna forget ♫
♫ Just let me live inside a dreamland ♫
♫ I wanna be free! ♫
♫ And let a brand new era dawn ♫
♫ I know that we can ♫
♫ Create a New World! ♫
♫ We can choose the way of our future ♫
♫ Try a brand new path ♫
♫ If I change the world... ♫
♫ This boundless music brings transformation ♫
♫ Messages within the song ♫
♫ Reach even further ♫
♫ This dream will come true ♫
♫ I believe in you ♫
♫ Say goodbye to everything that's weighing you down ♫
♫ Transcend beyond reality to colorful worlds of music ♫
♫ We need to keep on rising ♫
♫ Close your eyes and take my hand we're runnin' together ♫
♫ We don't have to live like this, I know we can all do better ♫
♫ I sing for liberation ♫
♫ You wanna play a real game, unfurl the chain ♫
♫ Melody lighting up the path to new horizons ♫
♫ Don't wanna cry, don't wanna try, wanna forget ♫
♫ Just let me live inside a dreamland ♫
♫ I wanna be free! ♫
♫ And let a brand new era dawn ♫
♫ I know that we can ♫
♫ Create a New World ♫
♫ We can choose the way of our future ♫
♫ Try a brand new path ♫
♫ If i change the world... ♫
♫ This boundless music brings transformation ♫
♫ Messages within the songs ♫
♫ Reach even further ♫
♫ A New Genesis ♫
Hey everyone I'm so glad we can finally meet! I'm Uta!
Sorry, it's just so much.
Uta we love you!
Everyone! Let's have fun today!
Ready, scumbags?
Yeah
If we can kidnap that star, wealth and fame will be ours. Sorry, Uta!
UTA! UTA!
Hey, Luffy!
Is he after Uta too?
It really is you!
Uta, you're Uta right?
its me! Me!
Me?
Could it be... Luffy?
Long time no see, Uta!
Hey, that straw hat!
Not the fifth emperor?
I can't be. Uta can't possibly be friends with a pirate!
Was Luffy an acquaintance of Uta's
That guy! if he is, he could've at least introduced us!
Why are you friends with Princess Uta?
What!!
You know, she's Shanks' daughter after all!
Shanks...?
A pirate, one of the Four Emperors. A beastly villain.
long ago, I remember
Yes, the very one who attacked Elegia.
Uta...
When i heard the venue was Elegia, I wondered what to do...
You're talking about the legend?
Yeah. But I never thought something even bigger than that would come of it..
What are you guys up for
The Fourth Emperor, Red-Haired Shanks has a daughter?
If that's true, you're going to be Red-head's biggest weakness.
We'll get a good price for you if we hand you over to some other powerful pirates!
So anyway, it's really too bad but the concert is cancelled!
Heat Beating
Bwo pop!
This girl is our catch now!
You're a... branch
Branch?
I'm Brulee! From the Big Mom Pirates!
Who's that beside her?
I'm Big Mom Charlotte Lin Lin's fourth son Oven This looks fun!Let me join in
Truly I came to see what the fuss was about and it's much more interesting than I expected!
Uta! Sorry but you're coming home with me as a souvenir!
Wait
it's okay.
Hey, hey! Targeting Uta? You trashpiles are gonna have to deal with me!
We can't allow such scoundrels to dirty such a lovely stage.
Things are finally getting interesting!
Don't underestimate the Jellyfish Pirates!
Song of scratches Blizzard Slice!
What a pity
The concert had only just begun
Let's do this! To protect Uta!
Okay! That's enough! Luffy and everyone! Thanks for protecting me! But the quarrel ends now!
Everyone is my fan, so get along enjoy the concert!
But Princess Uta, these guys are trying to kidnap you, you know?
If there's something we want we fight for it and we take it. We're pirates after all. Right?
Hey, everyone else you can stop being bad pirates too.
There are some things that are more important than your little songs!
♫ Now, let worry fall away ♫
♫ No fear allowed to stay ♫
♫ Your wish is now my dream And my hope never-ending ♫
♫ When clouds build up inside ♫
♫ My song can clear the sky You know I'm invincible ♫
♫ Everything will be alright. ♫
♫ I've got you by my side ♫
♫ My voice carries birds in flight ♫
♫ With ev'ry note, they go higher and higher ♫
♫ See how I move with such grace ♫
♫ Just like a dancer on the stage ♫
♫ Your voice carries life within ♫
♫ Calls me to action again and again ♫
♫ If you're hurt and you need me ♫
♫ I'll always be there I swear, I'll always protect you ♫
♫ We'll have the chance to go to brand new heights ♫
♫ You and I, unstoppable when we're together ♫
♫ We can have it all ♫
♫ 'Cause a fire burns within our hearts ♫
♫ Now, let us go hand in hand ♫
♫ To a light that lies ahead ♫
♫ All of our hopes and dreams ♫
♫ Can bring happiness when we're in sync ♫
♫ I've always felt this warmth from you ♫
♫ No one gives affection like you do ♫
♫ You make me invincible ♫
♫ When you here by my side ♫
♫ Strong with you by my side ♫
Everyone! The bad pirates have become a fun song now!
Now we have peace, so don't worry!
Yeah! They may be family but Shanks and Uta are different!!
You've gotten stronger, Uta!
I've never heard of it.
What's this!
What are you doing? We have to hurry back!
I have good news for everyone!
I always did livestreams with video transponder snails. I would always get tired and sleepy
and the concert would end quickly. This time, my concert will be endless I will go on forever.
Kyu?!
Yes! That means I can be together with everyone forever!
Everyone enjoying the show on the livestream! And everyone here at this venue! Let's have more and more fun!
Amazing!
She's going to continue the concert all on her own!
It's amazing!
UTA! UTA! UTA! UTA! UTA! UTA!
One more thing! This is important!
All you pirates! Marines and World Government people too! Don't get in the way of my concert!
Everyone is looking for fun things, happy things. If you do something awful, you better be ready
I'm Uta, the woman who will make a new generation! I'll make everyone happy with my songs!
Alright, on to the next song!
"Heads of the World Goverment, Five Elder Stars."
Red-Hair had a daughter, did he?
it's just like the Cipher Pol report said.
A new enemy who totally disavows the Great era of piracy has appeared.
It makes things complicated because the people are on her side.
We have to quickly nip this revolution in the bud or it will be too late.
Is that girl a descendant of Figarland?
I wonder about the existence of Tot Musica as well.
Tot Musica.
If that awakens again, being careful is not going to be enough.
MARIN
The subjugation of Uta has been decided. She's dangerous.
That's odd. Just one girl and the whole world is focusing on her.
Hey, are you underestimating her?
She's in Elegia, the island of music.
That's where the Tot Musica was sealed away in ancient times.
So, how many do you want to send?
How many ships can we send to Elegia immediately?
Thirty ships!
Alright. Take the companies and platoons and send out all the ships!
If the transponder snails can't be used, orders from the flagship will be done using flag signals, Signal Book Code 044, Each Ship already knows...
Captain, turn around immediately. Follow the signals and combine forces. Don't rush it. But gather your strength. Don't be lazy! Turn, turn, turn!
The airflow meter measures a four, a moderate breeze. The surface has long waves, with lots of whitecaps.
Reports from each vessel, each ship has a Each gunner assemble, check your cannons